

#### ULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOP

Bishopstown, Cork, Ireland

□ +33 6 99 78 19 49 | **□** rudy.murer.pro@gmail.com | **☆** rudymurer.com | **□** murerr | **□** Murerr

# Personal Profile

An eager, logical and detail-focused software developer with 3+ years of experience. Wide-ranging expertise in Web development, Android and Object-Oriented Programming. Team player, work closely with other developers through Git, and know what task to prioritize. Always enthusiastic and passionate to explain what has been produced during meetings. Applied multiple front-end frameworks like Angular and React but prefer Vue. Also familiar with NodeJS, Express and Symfony.

# Technical Skills \_\_\_\_\_

**PHP** Used PHP daily for server-side applications at ForWare.

**JavaScript** Worked on front-end JavaScript applications at ASA Brands.

**Vue.js** Produced modern client-side user interface and personal website with Vue.js.

**SQL** Queried and handled large data sets with MySQL for most projects.

**Kotlin** Used the kotlin language for severals Android application and Hackathon events.

**Android** Facilitated Android applications at Cansii, CIT and during personal projects.

**Java** Carried out short projects during the OOP Modules in France and Ireland.

**Python** Automated regular processes at ASA Brands with Python scripts.

**CI Tools** Deployed projects using pipelines with Gitlab, Github actions, Travis and Jenkins.

**Docker** Built microservices with Docker containers at ForWare.

# **Work Experience**

### **Full Stack Software Developer**

Cork, Ireland
Apr. 2019 - Now

#### **ASA Brands & ForWare**

(ASA Marketing manage both companies, they are located in the same office.)

- Resolved tickets and fixed bugs for the marketing team on ASA's in-house ERP built with PHP.
- Contributed to the development of new features for the fleet management system ForFleets.
- Facilitated and maintained web applications using Firebase and NUXTJS.
- Implemented a realtime fleet tracking system with Google Maps.
- Developed a web module to sort and filter companies artworks on image hash.
- Identified car registration plates with Google Vision API.
- Recorded videos with WebRTC MediaRecorder for ForFleets mobile users.
- Charged with the integration and mentoring of new developers and users.
- Learnt to quickly switch missions by using an issue tracking system.

#### **Android Internship**

Châteauneuf-sur-Isère, France

**CANSII** 

Apr. 2018 - Jun. 2018

- Developed a mobile application using Kotlin for MenuOnline Web users.
- Used a REST API & Retrofit to synchronize data.
- Understood the importance of CI tools and unit testing with Robotelectric.

### **PHP Internship**

8 FABLAB

Crest, France

Apr. 2017 - Jun. 2017

• Created a client-side interface for customers to book a training session.

- or extend of chieff state intended for customers to short a training session.
- Carried out an administration panel to manage bookings using Dolibarr ERP.
- Billed customers using Stripe API.

RUDY MURER · CURRICULUM VITAE

# **Education**

## **BSc in Software Development**

Cork, Ireland

2018 - 2019

**CORK INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - CIT** 

Final Year Project: Transport AI

- Developed a mobile and a Web application to book the nearest self-driving car.
- The data was stored and retrieved using Firebase.
- Google Maps API was used to display user location.

## **DUT Informatique**

Valence, France

2015 - 2018

Université Grenoble Alpes - UGA

(A two year university Diploma in Computing)

Final Year Project: Reprography App

- Established a web application that handle photocopies requests.
- The project was carried out using the Symfony Framework (PHP).
- Learnt the importance of the Model View Controller (MVC).

### **Baccalauréat STI2D SIN**

Valence, France

LYCÉE DES CATALINS

2015

(Leaving Certificat equivalent with special emphasis on Programming & Engineering.)

# Languages\_

French Native language

**English** Fluent

**Italian** Limited working proficiency

#### Interests

#### **Assistant Teacher**

Cork, Ireland

ALLIANCE FRANÇAISE CORK

June 2022 - Now

Volunteered to teach the French language to people from all ages as an assistant.

Voluteer Work

COMMUNITY HALL

2015 - 2016

Organization of French events and festivals in my hometown community hall.

Taught IT skills to seniors.

### **Extracurricular Activity**

#### **HOBBIES**

- Rock climbing & Kayaking
- Rubik's cube & Board Games (Chess, Magic TCG, Warhammer 40k)
- 3D Printing & AI (GPT-3, Wavenet, AlphaStar)

# Referees\_

**ForWare** Joady Sinnot, CTO of ForWare, joady.sinnot@forware.ie

**ASA Brands** Michelle Johnson, CEO of ASA Marketing, michelle.johnson@asamarketing.ie

**UGA** Karine Bergeron Pegoud, Guidance Counselor, karine.bergeron@univ-grenoble-alpes.fr

Cansii Cédric Angeniol, CEO of Cansii, cedric.angeniol@cansii.com